https://www.dharma.org/privacy-and-cookie-policy/

Search input field.
Donate
Toggle open the search bar.
Retreat Center
Dana (Generosity)
Forest Refuge
Dana (Generosity)
Benefits of Meditation
Interested in a Retreat?
Local Meditation Group
Search input field.
Toggle Navigation menu.
Toggle open the search bar.
Retreat Center
Dana (Generosity)
Forest Refuge
Dana (Generosity)
Benefits of Meditation
Interested in a Retreat?
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Insight Meditation Society (dharma.org) has a firm commitment to privacy. By using this website, you indicate your consent to all of the terms of this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with any term of this Privacy Statement, please do not use this website or submit any information to us through this website. We reserve the right to add to, change, or update this policy at any time.
This page also explains how dharma.org uses cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you visit our website. It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.
Privacy Statement
We do not collect any personal information unless you provide it to us on a voluntary basis. We collect the information that you provide – your name, address, telephone number, and/or email address via our retreat registration forms, donation form, balance payment form, volunteering forms, etc.
How We Use Information
Insight Meditation Society uses personal information collected on our site to update you about our services and news, to provide you with information that you request, and/or to improve our service offerings. If we would like to share your information with other companies or individuals in the future, we will obtain your express consent prior to sharing. We may disclose your personal information as needed if such information is requested by law enforcement agencies or if we are required to do so by law, regulation, subpoena, court order, or by a government agency or entity. We also may disclose personal information if disclosing that information is necessary to conduct investigations of possible illegality.
How We Protect Information
We take reasonable security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access to or unauthorized disclosure or destruction of data. We do not sell or lease your information to other companies or individuals without your permission. We may use IP addresses to protect the security and integrity of our site, to help troubleshoot and diagnose problems with our server, and to assist in the administration of our website.
Opting Out
Insight Meditation Society provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time. We will not send you an online newsletter or email communication unless you consent to receive such communications. If we propose to use your personal information for any purpose other than as described in this policy, we will offer you an opportunity to opt-out.
Users can opt-out from receiving newsletters and other emailed communications at any time. To unsubscribe, please email registration@dharma.org with “unsubscribe” in the subject line.
Cookie Policy
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the site again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information.
Cookies provide a convenience feature to save you time or to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you complete the contact form on our website, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.
Why We Use Cookies
Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to either enhance the experience on our site or enable us to identify usage patterns. For example, we use Google Analytics, Hotjar and GoSquared, third party platforms that measure our site’s performance and other statistics, to keep track of what pages you visit on our site to gauge potential interest patterns. If you’ve completed our contact form, it enables us to identify who you are, when you’ve visited, and what pages on our site you’ve viewed. We may use this data to either deliver customized content and/or promotions to users whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area, or to inform research activities for business development purposes.
Controlling Cookies
You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. You can set or change your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website with little to no discernible difference in your browsing experience. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser’s help menu for more information.
Updates to Policies
We may update this Privacy Statement and Cookie Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to the cookies we use or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons. Please revisit this page to stay informed about our privacy practices, use of cookies, and related technologies.
More Information
If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us at computer(at)dharma.org.
Sidebar Menu BIPOC Sangha Online Weekly Sitting Group
IMS Online Mini Retreats
IMS Retreat Center Teachers 2021
COVID-19 Update
IMS Book Club
IMS Daily Dharma
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Residential Fees
Join Our Mailing List
This form needs Javascript to display, which your browser doesn't support.
Sign up here instead
Support our teachers and our centers
Donate Now
Thank you for your kindness!
Copyright © 2020 Insight Meditation Society | Privacy Policy | Designed by Eri Design
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.
View Privacy PolicySETTINGSACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
